trafficbee.com 2003-06-20

# Southern California Highway Traffic Information

|    
---  
  
|   
---  
|    
---  
This statement discloses the privacy practices of the www.TrafficBee.com web site. Questions regarding this statement should be directed, via e-mail, to [support@trafficbee.com](mailto:support@trafficbee.com).  
   
TrafficBee.com's Privacy Philosophy  
**TrafficBee** offers a very tailored service and relies on customers, like you, to support its growth. While we understand the Internet is a rapidly changing communication medium, it should not come at the cost of individual choices to supplying personal information. New online activities raise new challenges, such as the privacy issues addressed in this policy. We believe that having a relationship with our customers that is founded on trust is good business. Any feedback you would like to provide to help us better meet your expectations in this area and our service, in general, is welcomed and appreciated.  
   
Information Collected by TrafficBee  
  
Trafficbee.com wants to make your online experience satisfying and safe. Our data collection policies allow you to choose how much personal information to provide to us, and to control how we use that information. Our goal is to provide you with a gratifying online experience while allowing you to control your privacy. When you register for our service, you will be asked at various times to provide information such as your name, email address, and/or information about how you travel. We request this information to provide our strongest value to you - a personalized service based on your driving patterns. TrafficBee customers find that they can save the most important gift - time.

**Information collected by TrafficBee can be categorized by as either anonymous or personally identifiable:**

**Anonymous Information** refers to information that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. For instance, viewing this page on our web site. We know how many individuals view it, but we do not necessarily know their names, where they live, or their date of birth. What we collect from transactions such as this is categorized anonymous information. 

**Personally Identifiable Information** refers to information that tells us specifically who you are, such as your name or e-mail address. We need this information to provide the personalized service that you have requested. We hope that, like many of our customers, you will find it beneficial to disclose this information. 

There are two primary sections in the TrafficBee where personal information is necessary. The first area where personal information is needed is when you subscribe to the basic service. Remember, the service is completely customized using your personal profile. Your information is necessary to deliver the service. The second area is if you choose to receive a RideGuide. The RideGuide is provided by the Southern California Association of Governments Commuter Services Department. This service is free and all your personal information is presented to SCAG to determine whether there are other individuals you may share a ride with.

The amount of Personally Identifiable Information that you choose to disclose to Trafficbee.com is completely up to you. The only way we know something about you personally is if you register for a personalized service or promotion. In other words, we will know Personally Identifiable Information about you only if you choose to share this type of information with us.

When you surf the Internet, your Internet browser (such as Netscape Navigator® or Microsoft Internet Explorer) automatically transmits some information to Trafficbee.com every time you access content on one of our sites. Examples of such information include the URL of the web page you were just on (known as the "Refer"), the IP (or Internet Protocol) address of the computer you are using, or the browser version you are using to access our site. All of this information is collected by Trafficbee.com and is used to help improve our offerings to you. For instance, we use this information to determine the fastest and most concise method possible for you to download the TrafficBee executable file to your computer - simplifying the entire download process.

To enable many of the features available within the TrafficBee sites, we will assign "cookies" to your Internet browser (such as Netscape Navigator or Microsoft Internet Explorer). A cookie is a small text file that contains a unique identification number stored on your computer. Cookies by themselves cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. This unique identification number automatically identifies your browser - but not you - to our server computers whenever you interact on one of our Internet domains. When you visit our site, a cookie is read by our server computers. Every web page that you access that includes advertising or content served from Trafficbee.com will have the contents of your cookie reported in our server logs. But only when you agree to provide Personally Identifiable Information directly to a TrafficBee branded service, such as through registration, will we be able to know anything about you other than the random number that our server computers originally assign to your browser.

There is a lot of confusion about cookies, how they are used, and what they can do. Cookies only contain information that the server computer "knew" in the first place, and can only be read by the serving domain that placed them. Cookies are an essential part of how the Internet works today, and allow server computers to recognize your computer's browser when you return. If you have ever gone to a web page that automatically provides personalized content without you having to "sign in," such as your own stock portfolio, this is almost certainly being accomplished with a cookie. Since cookies are only text files, they cannot "run" on your computer and have no ability to search your computer for other information, or transmit it to anyone.

Cookies are part of the technology implemented by your web browser. But don't just take our word for it - read what the companies who wrote the browsers have to say!

For Netscape, please visit: [  
http://home.netscape.com/security/basics/privacy.shtml#cookies](http://home.netscape.com/security/basics/privacy.shtml#cookies)

For Microsoft, please visit: [http://www.microsoft.com/insider/internet/articles/security2.htm#cookies ](http://www.microsoft.com/insider/internet/articles/security2.htm#cookies%20)  

What Organization Is Collecting The Information?  
The data you provide Trafficbee.com is collected by [CeroView, LLC](http://www.ceroview.com/). Trafficbee.com is a wholly owned-subsidiary of this corporation. Click here to find information about [CeroView](http://www.ceroview.com/).  
   
How The Information Is Used  
  
Our services have been designed to enable Trafficbee.com to provide hyper-local, personally relevant traffic and related content to those customers who wish to receive it. Our ability to provide enhanced services and content to our customers is dependent on our ability to provide venues for our partners that reach specific demographic segments of our customer base. Generally, our partners have little interest in reaching a specific customer of our services \- they are more interested in making sure their information is reached within a geographic area. As a matter of policy we provide no mechanism for a partner to reach you or any other specific customer, directly. Instead, our partners have the need to reach customers who share common demographic characteristics such as a specific commute route. For instance, we may send broadcasts directed to TrafficBee subscribers in south Orange County regarding a construction project. Any subscriber commuting through that corridor will receive the notice. 

Below is a description of the uses of the information that we collect and how our visitors and partners benefit from broadcast:

We provide personalized content in the form of traffic conditions, construction information, road maintenance, commuter information, camera images, and more to our users. We pay attention to what our customers do and do not use on our service and modify our content appropriately. The creation of your profile allows Trafficbee.com to match your demographic characteristics and commuter profile, without ever knowing that customer's name or any other Personally Identifiable Information about them. These anonymous profiles are used to target advertising - primarily banners - to those customers, both on the Trafficbee.com domain and any of the other Internet domains where we serve advertising. Through the use of anonymous profiles, Trafficbee.com can serve advertising to our customers that is more likely to be for products they would want, and sell that advertising for a higher price. This is essential to our ability to provide high quality content to our customers for free. 

Trafficbee.com never matches "Who you are" with "Where you've been" on the Internet because we do not use personal data characteristics such as your name, address or phone number to create these anonymous profiles but rather use primary demographic characteristics such as your age or gender. Finally, anonymous profiles present no privacy risk to our customers because they are worthless to third parties. Since any potential third party would be unable to read the cookies that we set on our domains, only Trafficbee.com can create value from these anonymous profiles.

We develop summary - but not individual - reports for our advertisers. An example of a summary report might be "12,000 people clicked on Advertisement 'X' today, and of those people, 35% had previously indicated they had an interest in sports." Our advertisers, who make it possible for you to use Trafficbee.com for free, need this information to determine how effective their advertising investments are. We never tell our advertisers who it was that saw or clicked on their advertisements, unless you have specifically told us it is acceptable to do so.  

Information Distribution  
  
If you are providing us Personally Identifiable Information, it will only be used within TrafficBee. 

Some partners place notices on our site and may collect information about you when you view or click on their notice or content through the use of cookies (using the same techniques as described above). Due to the way the Internet technically operates, we cannot control this collection of information \- but we can control which organizations are allowed to place such notices on our site. It should be noted that anyone placing notices on our web sites can only collect browser type and IP information. You are not required to provide any partner personal information unless you choose to do so.

In some cases, we use third-party advertising companies to serve notices when you visit our Web site. Our third-party advertising company also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering notices to this Site. 

Our server computers will retain whatever Personally Identifiable Information you have provided to us, however; and it is potentially available for distribution to third parties - most obviously law-enforcement agencies acting under subpoena power, per the terms of this section of our Privacy Policy. Although unlikely, Trafficbee.com may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information the appropriate governmental authorities. If requested by law enforcement or judicial authorities, we will provide this information upon receipt of the appropriate documentation. We do not use this information to target any notices to our customers, nor is it ever willingly distributed to any third party, such as an advertiser, except if subpoenaed.

Trafficbee.com offers affiliates the opportunity to host the TrafficBee notifyer for download, and to receive branding or other consideration in return for helping us increase the number of users for our product(s). If you have downloaded the TrafficBee notifyer from an affiliate, the registration information that you provide is shared with the affiliate. Please check the affiliate's own Privacy Policy to determine their information distribution policies.

Finally, Trafficbee.com does not control the information collection and distribution policies on Internet domains other than its own.   

What Choices Are Available Regarding Collection, Use, And Distribution Of The Information?  
  
Trafficbee.com does offer you the ability to control the email communications and notices that are made to you. It is our intention to give you as much control over the information you receive. 

If you do choose to share Personally Identifiable Information with Trafficbee.com, you can control the level of information you receive. At anytime you may update to your information, your profile and you TrafficBee notifyer. Any time information is requested from you on from Trafficbee.com you should see a clear indication that it is an official communication of TrafficBee. Trafficbee.com will always give you a chance to unsubscribe to any email communication from us - clear directions for doing so will appear in any email message we send to you. At times, Trafficbee.com may enter into co-branding arrangements with our partners or other companies, and if so, an opt-in question may be present for contact from these firms as well. 

Trafficbee.com does reserve the right to send a one-time registration confirmation email, and infrequent Service Alert messages to its customers to inform them of specific changes that may impact their ability to use a service they have previously signed up for. We may periodically contact you regarding new or upgraded services or product offerings. We reserve the right to contact you if compelled to do so as part of a legal proceeding or if there has been a violation of our Terms of Service. Trafficbee.com is retaining these rights because in limited cases we feel that we may need the right to contact you as a matter of law or regarding matters that will be important to you.  

What Kind Of Security Procedures Are In Place To Protect Against The Loss, Misuse, Or Alteration Of Information Under The Company's Control?  
Trafficbee.com operates secure data networks protected by industry standard firewalls and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced or upgraded as necessary. Only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our customers.  

---  
  
* * *  
  
[Real-Time Traffic](http://www.trafficbee.com/resources/realtime.shtml) | [Construction Info](http://www.trafficbee.com/resources/construction.shtml) | [Commuter Info](http://www.trafficbee.com/commuter_info/carpool.shtml) | [Transportation Links  
](http://www.trafficbee.com/resources/links.shtml)[Privacy Policy](http://www.trafficbee.com/about/privacy_policy.shtml) | [Disclaimer](http://www.trafficbee.com/about/disclaimer.shtml) | [Copyright Notice ](http://www.trafficbee.com/about/copyright.shtml)
